GYEONGSEONG CREATURE
It's always the same pattern.
I'm overcome with hunger
after extreme blood loss or exhaustion.
- I need to feed.
This is bad.
You will only experience good luck
from now on.
BUGANG COMPANY
VICE PRESIDENT JANG HO-JAE
CALL ME
BUGANG COMPANY
GYEONGSEONG CREATURE
BETWEEN MEMORY AND OBLIVION
EPISODE 3
PIECES OF MEMORIES
BUGANG COMPANY
Have a seat.
Do you want something to drink?
Coffee? Or something else?
Let's talk first.
Let's do introductions first.
I already told you my name.
What's yours?
I don't have one.
We're on the same side,
but you won't even tell me your name?
Since we're on the same side,
we can skip the trivialities.
How's your injury?
Are you all right?
You were seriously hurt that day.
I'd like to set just two rules.
No personal questions.
And you do as I say.
No introductions and no catching up?
You're one unfriendly teammate.
I'm going to call Madam Na's phone now.
But Madam Na's dead.
The person who killed her has her phone.
He was also the last person
to request a job.
What was the job?
Look familiar?
What are you doing?
You're on probation. Don't wander around.
Give me a break.
Do you mean to lock me up
until I'm a living corpse?
If that's the only way
to control a variable like you, yes.
What are you so afraid of?
That's why you keep trying
to suppress and control us.
You're scared
that we'll be a threat.
Is that why Ho-jae
had to go through surgery?
He got on my nerves.
He was getting in the way.
He was annoying.
That's why.
Do you really think you can control us?
I do know how to control
the Najin inside your head.
Go back to your room.
Actually, I met one of our kind outside.
SILVERBILL
It's her.
Hello?
Are you looking for me?
Do you know me?
How?
Is she with you?
Amazing.
So she's alive after all that.
She really must be one of my kind.
What are you talking about?
I'm sure you know what I mean.
I don't. That's why I asked.
So spell it out.
What did you mean?
Answer me.
- Who was that?
- Ho-jae.
He's with her right now.
What do we do? Call him again?
Let's wait.
Hey.
He said that you were "one of his kind."
Do you know what he meant by that?
You're one of us.
No.
MADAM NA
LET US MEET TONIGHT
It's him.
He wants to meet.
CHOOSE A LOCATION
Done.
That's all I needed from you.
"That's all"?
I'll be going alone.
Are you kidding me?
Didn't I just help you set up the meeting?
Look.
I'm the one being framed as a suspect.
I'm the one he wants to meet.
There are some things
you should never encounter in your life.
Get involved with them, and in a flash,
your life will become hell.
You can't revert that…
or return to the past.
You may have to live your whole life
like you're in an endless nightmare.
Are you threatening me
or worrying about me?
I'm seriously trying to dissuade you.
You can't handle that guy.
Then call the police.
My goal is to catch him,
not to escalate the situation.
What if we call the police
and he decides to hide away?
Then it'd be a lost cause.
He's looking for me.
He wants to meet me, not you.
Recklessness isn't the same
as bravery, you know.
I'd rather die before I let anyone
walk into danger by themselves.
You said we're on the same side.
So we go together.
Are they going to meet up?
Yes, they will make contact
with the suspect who has Madam Na's phone.
Time and place?
Not confirmed yet.
I'm planning on tailing them.
I'll request backup.
Follow them when they're on the move.
Wait, what are you gonna do?
Who did you say you're meeting?
The guy who killed the Owl Bar owner.
She thinks
he's behind the motel murder too.
Then call the cops.
You shouldn't be going there!
If we call the cops and he finds out,
he'll go deeper into hiding,
and it'll be a lost cause.
Says who?
She does.
And you trust her?
How many times have you met her?
Not sure. Maybe twice?
Hey.
Do you even know what her name is?
- Ms. Silverbill?
- What does she do?
She finds missing people.
I knew it!
Everything about her
is vague, uncertain, and unclear.
But you're going to follow her blindly
without question?
This isn't like you.
I know.
But strangely, I find myself believing
whatever she says.
Because you've fallen for her looks!
Snap out of it, man!
What are you gonna do
if she turns out to be an accomplice?
What if they're playing you?
Her closest friend was murdered.
Yong-gil, put yourself in her shoes.
If someone murdered me so violently,
wouldn't you lose your mind?
Wait, why are you making this about us?
I feel very offended.
Would you lose your mind or not?
I'd lose it, man!
Would you look for the culprit like crazy?
Yeah, I so would!
- Will you be our backup later?
- Yeah, I will--
Thanks, man.
You crazy son of a… Damn you!
Make sure you dress warmly.
Hold on.
It's three times.
I've seen her three times already.
Is that you, Jong-hyeok?
Yes, Grandma. I'm home.
Goodness. You must be tired.
- I'm fine.
- Well done today.
Go wash your hands.
- Let's eat first.
- Okay.
So, your training starts tomorrow?
Yeah, it goes on for a month.
What kind of training takes a full month?
I heard all new employees go through it.
Grandma, what's this?
What?
What else? It's a new suit.
I received a bonus!
Really? From Madam Na?
No, from Master Jang.
Master… who?
Don't worry about it.
Have a seat. Let's eat.
Okay.
You cooked so much food!
AHN JONG-HYEOK, MULTI-SUPPORT TEAM
JEONSEUNG BIOTECH
You won't be having home-cooked meals
for a while now, that's why.
Ho-jae.
I'm telling you one more time--
I'll be back.
Scared?
No. Not at all.
Someone's got fancy gadgets.
It's two-way.
And these.
If things look bad,
throw them hard on the ground.
They'll go off on their own.
Where did you get equipment like this?
Are you a retired soldier?
A former NIS agent or something?
They're effective
for two to three minutes each,
so you'll buy enough time to get back
to the car if you use them in intervals.
Again with the mixed messages.
Are you worrying about me
or threatening me?
I'm saying let's not slow each other down.
Why do you keep your name a secret anyway?
Do you have a hang-up about your name?
Or do you carry a secret
that you can't divulge?
Ms. Silverbill.
Can you hear me?
Hello?
- Mic check--
- Focus, will you?
Okay. Roger that.
I guess he's already here.
Moving toward R2.
Ms. Silverbill,
are you on your way?
Where are you?
Ms. Silverbill.
What was that?
I think we walked into a trap.
You need to run away.
Now!
Where are you now? Are you okay?
I'm on my way. Keep running!
Hold on a sec.
Jang Ho-jae, you idiot.
This way!
What are those things? Are they human?
Let's get out of here first.
This is my fight from now on.
What does that mean?
If you're here, I can't fight properly.
What?
I'm sorry.
And who the heck are you?
Hi.
Ho-jae.
It's been so long.
No, wait.
We met briefly last time.
When I stabbed that woman.
Are you the one called Silverbill?
Tell me who you are
before you ask questions.
What the hell are you bastards?
Are you with the guy who killed Madam Na?
You bastard.
Were you that scared?
What was that swarm of people
that I just saw?
I heard you had surgery.
I just came to check
if all your memories really disappeared…
and if there really is nothing left.
Fucking assholes.
This isn't what we agreed.
Man, that was boring.
Is that all you got?
Keep going.
Keep going, you asshole.
Those who came here today
are all gonna die.
No. Don't do it.
Don't, you bastard!
Master Jang.
No…
Are you all right?
Master Jang.
No.
Stay with me.
No!
End them now.
You have to get up. No.
No, please. Wake up!
Ho-jae, get in quickly!
After them!
Forget it.
There's no need.
They'll soon find out…
what it is that they rescued.
Is she dead?
Tell me! Is the woman dead?
God, this is messed up!
- What's going on?
- Let's go to the hospital.
- What? The hospital?
- Step on it.
- Floor it!
- The hospital? Just wait.
What?
What's happening?
Are you all right?
She hasn't fully recovered
from the injury two days ago.
I need to feed.
Add to that more enormous blood loss
due to the exact same injury.
It'd be near impossible for her
to resist the hunger and thirst.
I need to feed.
You're losing a lot of blood.
We have to stem it first.
Stop the car!
- Stop the car!
- What are you doing?
- Stop!
- Are you out of your mind?
- Let me go!
- Don't do this!
Yong-gil.
Yong-gil, are you okay?
Yong-gil, wake up.
I need to feed.
- I need to feed.
This is bad.
Ms. Silverbill!
I need to feed.
- What's wrong?
- I need--
Get away from me!
I'm sorry.
Get away from me.
Don't come close.
You have to go to the hospital.
You might actually die!
Before I do!
Before I do…
I might end up killing you.
I might end up attacking you, so please…
please just go.
Please…
I don't know why I'm acting like this.
But…
a name came to me just now.
Ms. Yoon Chae-ok.